dayz.com 2013-05-24

# Dayzee

This policy was last updated on 3 February 2011

This privacy policy describes how dayzee and it's owners treat the personally identifiable information that is collected about you when you visit the web sites to which this policy is linked.  This is a legal document that sets out how dayzee handles data which identifies you. You should read it in conjunction with the dayzee Terms and conditions, of which this Privacy Policy forms part. 

1\. Information other users can see

dayzee is here to keep your information confidential! That's why there are only two types of   
information you will be sharing with others when you register with dayzee:  
a.    Registered dayzee users will be able to tell whether you have registered with dayzee   
(otherwise they might keep trying to invite you).  
b.    You and the other users will only be notified of your mutual feelings (wanting to go on a date or consider each other true friends) if you both include each other on your lists of friends.   
In no other circumstances, will any user of dayzee be able to tell what information you have included in your Details or which other people you have included on your various Lists.

2\. Emails from dayzee 

Service Emails. The team at dayzee hate spam and will not send you unsolicited emails. But there are some emails that we will need to send you to make dayzee work. These include notifications that you someone has added you to a list, email account validation emails and guides on how to use the site. A full list of the types of emails you will receive are shown below:   
*    Validation emails - the email we use to verify each of your email addresses when you register   
*    Welcome emails - emails which explain how to use the site when you first join   
*    Match emails - emails which notify you if you have been included on someone else's "Date" or "Friends" list  
*    Key service messages - if we need to notify you about changes to the service   
*    Payment receipt - this is sent if you upgrade to Full Membership   
*    Renewal notices - these remind you to renew your Full Membership   
*    Service suspension notices - if you break the house rules   
*    Newsletters

When registering, you are given the option to receive our occasional newsletter. We use this to notify you about new features on the site, ask your opinion, and tell you about services you might not be using yet. Generally you'll get a newsletter about once every four weeks.   
If you decide you no longer want to receive these newsletters all you need to do is change your setting under your <My Profile>. 

2\. The information we gather and track 

When you register on dayzee, you provide your name (including a previous name, where relevant), one or more email addresses (each is registered) and some optional notes about yourself ("Registration Information"). They are available to you, and capable of being changed, through the <My Profile> page. 

3\. Cookies

a.    We use small files known as "cookies" to enhance Members' experience of the dayzee as follows:    
To hold Members' login information, so that your category listings are displayed when you visit the dayzee.  To facilitate optimal use of the dayzee by Members, by means of a temporary "session" cookie. These cookies disappear when the Member's browser session ends, or if the Member clicks the "logoff" text, which appears on the dayzee. 

b.    We use an external, independent measurement and research company to track our site   
usage.  Further details about the company may be obtained on request.  They use cookies and code on the site to gather non-personal data regarding the number and frequency of visitors to our site.  Both the cookies and the embedded code provide general site and not personal statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site and other general information. Dayzee uses this type of information to help it improve the services to its members. 

c.    Third party cookies including those from Google are used on some parts of the site. They are used for tracking the success of advertising campaigns. These cookies are normally permanent. 

4\. Sharing and use of information 

The over-riding principles we apply are these: 

a.    We, and (where relevant) our credit card processing agents, will not supply your personal data to a third party for commercial exploitation - thus, you can rest assured that we will not sell the lists of our Members' email addresses to a third party; and 

b.    the only circumstances in which we will provide any of your personal data to a third party for non-commercial purposes are those contained in this Privacy Policy. 

*    Registration Information. Once a Member registers with dayzee, only the fact that she or he is registered will be available to, and searchable by, users of dayzee. 

*    Messaging through dayzee. We do not directly make your email address available to anyone on any screen of dayzee. The only legitimate way of making contact with a friend found on dayzee is for both Members to enter each other on their respective "Secret Lists" a message will then sent to both Members. We will notify the addressee Member, using the email address he/she has provided to us, that dayzee is holding a message for him/her, and the Member can read the message when logged into dayzee.  Members may check and (if required) change the email address we hold for them at any time through <My Profile>. Sent and received messages may appear in a Member's Inbox on dayzee for an indefinite period - we do not delete it after any specific period. However, this does not mean that we will retain your messages forever; there may come a time when we will need to delete some or all of it, for technical or other reasons. In this event, we will endeavour to give you advance warning that we are going to do so. 

*    dayzee may include interactive advertising for other businesses. We may use, and provide to third parties, anonymised demographic data provided by Members to target this advertising more appropriately. 

*    dayzee does not hold any credit card information. Should we use online services, these will be externally managed by reputable firms. 

*    We may share data supplied by you (or collected about you) with subsidiaries and other companies related to dayzee, but only for the purposes described in this policy. 

*    Changes in dayzeeâ€™s business. If all of the assets which dayzee uses to operate its business (or substantially all of them) are acquired by a third party, we may transfer personal data we then hold to that party so that the acquirer can continue to provide the dayzee service. 

*    Place of processing. The personal information held by us is held on and processed by   
computers situated in the United Kingdom and United States of America. 

5\. Security 

We have security measures in place to protect our customer database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each Member's responsibility: 

*    to protect against unauthorised access to Your Details

*    to ensure no-one else uses the dayzee on that Member's machine while it is "logged on" to dayzee

*    to log off or exit from the dayzee when not using it

*    to keep his/her password secret

6\. Removing yourself from dayzee

You may have your registration details removed at any time. To remove yourself please use the <Contact Us> link and we will remove all Your Details. 

7\. Disclosure for legal reasons 

We reserve the right to communicate such of a Member's personal information, other than members "Date" and "Friends" lists information, as we hold to third parties which seek the disclosure of it, and which make a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.  

8\. Data Retention Period

We will retain your personal data only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which you consent under the dayzee Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, or as is required by applicable law, and then we will delete it. 

    9\. Contacting dayzee

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the dayzee, or your dealings with dayzee, please use the  <Contact Us> link. You can also use the form if you wish to request from dayzee a copy of the personal data we hold about you or a description of that data. Please note that by law we are entitled to charge you a small sum for providing this information. 

10\. Links to third party sites 

Dayzee contains links to other sites. dayzee is not responsible for the privacy practices, or the content, of those web sites. 

11\. Data Protection Information 

Upon completion of the beta test, we will be registering with the UK Data Protection agency. You can obtain further information about data protection laws by visiting the Information Commissioner's website at www.dataprotection.gov.uk . 

12\. Changes to this Privacy Policy 

dayzee may change this policy from time to time in its discretion during the beta testing period of the site.  Your continued use of our site indicates your consent to this Privacy Policy and any amended versions of it. Upon completion of the beta test, if we change this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of the changed document in the same way as we notify changes to the dayzee Terms and Conditions.
